var questionArray = [
{question:"Please speak __ little louder",
a:"a",
b:"an",
c:"the",
d:"(nothing)",
answer:"a",

},
{question:"He is one of __ smartest people I know",
a:"a",
b:"an",
c:"the",
d:"(nothing)",
answer:"the"
},
{question:"How __ factories are in your area",
a:"much",
b:"some",
c:"any",
d:"many",
answer:"many"
},
{question:"__ pupils can answer this question",
a:"Little",
b:"A little",
c:"Few",
d:"A few",
answer:"Few"
},
{question:"We plan to go __ a picnic next saturday",
a:"on",
b:"at",
c:"in",
d:"with",
answer:"on"
},
{question:"Our father is standing __ the gate.",
a:"by",
b:"between",
c:"next",
d:"for",
answer:"by"
},
{question:"She told us __ her new projects.",
a:"about",
b:"at",
c:"for",
d:"to",
answer:"about"
},
{question:"He is __ the computer.",
a:"to using",
b:"using",
c:"use",
d:"uses",
answer:"using"
},
{question:"__ he play baseball after school?",
a:"Is",
b:"Do",
c:"Does",
d:"Has",
answer:"Does"
},
{question:"__ month is the Chinese new year?",
a:"When",
b:"What",
c:"Where",
d:"How",
answer:"What"

}]